Yes.
はーい
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
It's been a while.
お久しぶり
How have you been?
元気あった?
I was fine.
元気でした
good.
よかった
We met again.
また会えた
You look cute today too.
今日も可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Didn't it feel quiet and rough?
静粗感がしたんじゃない?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
nice.
いいね
That's cute.
それ可愛い
It's like checking.
チェック的な感じで
Come inside.
中入って
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's been a long time.
お 久 しぶり
お久しぶりです
good.
よかった
See you again.
また会えて
I thought it might be quiet and rough today,
今日、 静粗っぽいかなって思ったけど、
It's surprisingly naughty.
意外とすごい エッチなの
The spines are a little short.
トゲがちょっと短め
Beautiful feet.
綺麗な足が
Wow, it looks outstanding.
すごい、際立って見える
If you were to walk around town wearing such clothes, wouldn't it be difficult to get people to look at you?
そんな服で街中歩いてたら、 視線とか大変なんじゃない?
not at all.
全然
Probably not.
多分そんなことないよ
perhaps?
多分?
I'm being watched a lot.
めっちゃ見られてるよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
There's a lot of damage behind the escalator.
エスカレーターとか 後ろでめっちゃかかんでる
There are a lot of uncles.
おじさんとかたくさんいるよ
There's a huge line.
めっちゃ行列できてる
It looks like a ribbon.
リボンみたいになってるね
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いですよね
Looks a lot like a giraffe.
めっちゃキリンちゃんみたい
I feel like I've been to Piroland even though I haven't been there yet.
行 ってないのに、 ピロランドに行った気分になる
That's great.
最高だよね
It's like I'm trying so hard.
努めるへんな感じでね
You can feel happy.
幸せな気分になれる
It's frippy and it's good.
ふりっぷいし、いいんだよね
cute.
可愛い
It's a mess.
め ちゃ くちゃ
I'm having so much fun playing Mace today.
今日のさ、 メースプレイさ、 楽しみすぎてさ、
It's really, really bad.
めっちゃさ、 やばいんだよね
Since you went the other day,
この前、 行 ってくれてからさ、
Only mace people do it.
メース者でしか おんなにしてない
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I keep imagining how he will play.
ずっと想像しながら どんなプレイしてくれるのかな?
It seems so.
そうみたいな
Actually, I've never been to Mace.
実はさ、 メース行ったことないんだよね
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
first time.
初めて
What does Mace do?
メースって、 どんなことする?
Massage is the main thing.
マッサージがメインですね
How far will you massage?
どこまでマッサージしてくれるの?
Even to the point where it's a bit risqué.
ちょっと際どいところまで
Even to the point.
際どいところまで
However, there is no such thing.
ところはやんないんだ
I don't like the racy parts.
際どいところはやんないんだ
It's even close to the point.
際どいところまでなんだ
I agree.
そうですね
But, you know, when I watch movies,
でもさ、なんかさ、 映画とか見てるとさ、
I'll do it till the end.
最後までやっちゃうじゃん
surely.
確かに
Actually, I haven't done it.
実際さ、 やってないの
I wonder what it is.
どうなんだろう
Maybe it's for girls.
女の子にやるのかもしれないですね
picture?
え?
Are you doing it?
やってる?
It's a secret.
秘密です
secret?
秘密?
Is it a secret?
秘密なの?
It's a secret.
秘密です
There's a possibility that it's a secret.
秘密ってことはなんか、 可能性ありそう
I was wondering if it was that kind of shop.
そういうお店なのかなと思ってた
I can do it till the end.
最後までできる
It's different, but it's different.
一応違うけど、 違うんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
I was given a nuru massage on the bed,
なんか、ベッドの上で、 ぬるぬるマッサージしてもらって、
I thought it would be like that.
そのままって感じだと思ってた
If it's soap or something, let it get slimy in the bath,
なんか、ソープとかだったら、 お風呂でぬるぬるして、
Like.
みたいな
surely.
確かに
I think it's just a bed version, not a bath version.
お風呂バージョンじゃなくて、ベッドバージョンってだけだと思
It was.
った
That's not what I mean.
そう いうわけじゃないんだ
That's right.
そうなんですよね
Give me a massage.
マッサージして
What do you look like when you're giving me a massage?
マッサージしてるときは、 ど んな格好してるの?
Yeah, but there are a lot of things.
えー、でもいろいろ
various?
いろいろ?
I do a lot of things.
いろんなことしてます
picture?
え?
Are you wearing clothes?
服は着てる?
Well, I'm wearing it just in case.
えっと、一応着てます
Are you wearing it?
着てるんだ?
Are you wearing regular clothes, not underwear?
下着とかじゃなくて、普通に服着てる?
There is something like a uniform.
一応、制服みたいなのがあります
Did you see anything?
なんか、見た?
It looked like a uniform.
制服っぽかった
But, I'm not wearing a uniform today.
でもね、 今日は制服じゃなくてね、
There are clothes you want me to wear.
着てほしい服があるんだよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Well, I brought it, so I'd like you to wear it.
それさ、持ってきたからさ、 ちょっとそれ着てほしいんだけど
Well, okay?
さ、 いい?
This is it, and I can't help but imagine myself wearing it.
これなんだけど、 これを着てる姿を めっちゃ想像して、
I got excited.
興奮しちゃった
Now, here, try changing your clothes.
今、ここでさ、 着替えてみてよ
To this?
これに?
Can I have you change your clothes?
着替えてもらってもいい?
A girl's changing clothes makes my heart flutter.
女の子の生着替え ドキドキしちゃう
Unlike last time, your underwear is really sexy, isn't it?
この前と違ってさ、 下着さ、めっちゃセクシーじゃない?
Today it's black.
今日は黒です
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいね
What a day.
何この日も
I'll show you my back.
後ろ姿見せてやる
a little bit.
ちょっと
Wow, behind me.
うわ、後ろ
It doesn't seem like it.
あるようでないよ
Isn't it see-through?
スケスケじゃない?
Do naughty people wear this on a regular basis?
こんなさ、 エッチな人にさ、普段から着けてんの?
Where do you buy it?
どこで買ってんの?
But I probably spend a lot of time on the internet.
でも私結構、ネットとかが多いかもしれない
Is that so?
そうなの?
On the internet?
ネットで?
There are so many different things out there.
いろんなの出てるから
How do I search to find out?
なんて調べたら出てくるの?
Sexy rangel?
セクシー系の ランジェル?
I'm choosing something sexy.
セクシー系を選んでるんだ
I'm choosing.
選んでます
Why did you choose something sexy?
なんでセクシー系選んじゃうの?
I think it's better to be sexy.
セクシーなほうがいいかな
picture?
え?
Is it for someone to see?
それは誰かに見てもらうため?
I like my cute style.
自分かわいいスタイル好きです
Is it okay to wear what I'm wearing?
自分が着けてるのはいいの?
Have someone look at it?
人に見てもらって?
Maybe both.
どっちもかも
What kind of people are you seeing?
どんな人に見てもらってんの?
Didn't you just say that you don't have a boyfriend?
さっき彼氏いないって言ってたじゃん?
sex friend?
セフレ?
There aren't many people like that now.
今はあんまりそういう人もいないから
Who are you showing it to?
誰に見せてんのかな?
Which underwear is better than my underwear from before?
さっきの自分の下着とどっちがイッチ?
This one is better.
こっちのほうがイッチ
The previous one was pretty hot though.
さっきのもだいぶイッチだったけどね
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
He seemed very adult-like just now,
さっきのはすごい大人っぽかったけど、
This is a little loli-like,
これは これでちょっとロリっぽさというか、
cute.
か わいい
It's a cute type.
かわいい系だね
Wow, so naughty yet so cute.
すごい、 すごいイッチなのにかわいいって
That's amazing.
すごいね
Isn't it the strongest?
最強じゃない?
I have beautiful legs, so tights look great on me.
足がきれいだからタイツがすごい似合うね
Do you mean tights now?
今ってタイツって言う?
It's called tights.
タイツって言う
It was over.
ふがて終わった
I thought my uncle had left.
おじさん出ちゃったかなって
There's a lot of different ways of saying things now.
いろいろ今言い方違うじゃん
It's called stockings.
ストッキングとか言うよね
That's right.
そうだ よね
difficult.
難しい
Clothes for girls are difficult.
女の子の服って大変だよね
Cute though.
かわいいけど
Like a rattle belt.
ガタベルトみたいな
But it's amazing, I can put it on right away when I see it.
でもすごいね、それの見て、 すぐパッて着れちゃう
After all, aren't you wearing something like this on a regular basis?
普段からやっぱりこういうの着てるんじゃない?
This is not much.
これはあんまり
Is this too much?
これはあんまり?
There aren't too many rattling belts though.
ガタベルトとかあんまりだけど
Do you cosplay?
コ スプレはする?
I also cosplay, but only a few times.
コスプレもでも 何回かしかないです
How many times?
何回か?
Why did you wear it?
何で着たの?
Uniforms, etc.
制服とか
Looks good on me.
似合いそう
What uniform?
何の制服?
Sailor suit.
セーラー服
Oh no.
やば
It definitely suits you.
絶対似合うじゃん
It probably gives me a youthful feeling.
一緒に多分、それ 青春感じれるね
I'd like to go somewhere on my bike with you.
一緒に自転車でも どっか行きたいよね
Did you wear anything other than a sailor suit?
セーラー服以外に何か着た?
A maid or something.
メイドさんとか
It definitely suits you.
絶対似合うじゃん
I want it to be suspended.
休止されたいよね
By the way, are you supposed to add milk to your coffee?
ちなみに、 コーヒーにはミルク入れるはずですか?
I'm a fan of adding milk.
私、ミルク入れる派です
cute.
かわいい
Do you dislike bitterness?
苦いの苦手?
I'm not good at it.
苦手ですね
That's right.
そう なんだ
I don't like bitter things.
苦いの苦手なんだ
Don't you like men's drinks too?
男の人のあれも飲むの苦手?
It's a secret.
秘密です
What kind of secret is it?
秘密ってことはどんなことある?
there is.
あります
Was it bitter?
苦かった?
I hear it's bitter.
苦いって聞くじゃん
It might have been bitter.
苦かったかも
Did you add sugar?
お 砂糖入れた?
I haven't put it in.
入れてない
That's right, it would be nice to have a ribbon to attach it to.
そういうね、 組み付けるリボンとかいいよね
cute.
かわいい
Is it already completed?
もう 完成してきた?
Did you wear it?
着れた?
Yeah.
うん
The key is that there are a lot of ribbons.
リボン多めなのがポイントだよね
surely.
確かに
Is this the set?
セットのもいっか
It suits you.
似合ってるね
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいい
It's so see-through.
スケスケだよ
copper?
どう?
cute.
かわいい
Which is better: cute or embarrassing?
かわいいのと恥ずかしいの、 ど っちが勝ってる?
About half and half.
半々くらい
It's cute how you look shy.
照れてる姿もかわいいね
Now, just look at how cute it is.
もうさ、 そのかわいいのさ、 見てるだけさ、
Look at this.
見てよこれ
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
It's already moving.
もう動いてるよ
It's true.
本当だ
Please say hello.
ご挨拶してみてよ
What's going on?
どうなってる?
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
As cute as it is, it gets bigger.
かわいいだけ大きくなっちゃう
What can you do for me?
どうしてくれる?
I drank it right away.
すぐ飲みちゃったね
I like it.
好 きだね
Try using just your mouth.
お口だけにしてみて
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Put it all the way in yourself.
自分で奥まで入れて
What's next?
次はどうする?
You look so naughty.
すっごいエッチな顔してるね
It hurts so bad.
すごい痛い
It's like breathing it in.
吸い込むようにそうだよ
I can't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなっちゃう
Let's play mace soon.
そろそろメイスごっこしようか
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
I want you to be the floor.
床になってほしい
On the floor?
床に?
You're a great massager.
すごいマッサージ上手だね
Do you usually want to give someone a massage outside of work?
普段仕事以外でもマッサージとか してあげたいとかするの?
I might give it to you once in a while.
たまにしてあげたりするかも
A boyfriend?
彼氏とか?
A real massage for a friend.
リアルに 友達とかに ガチのマッサージ
Seriously?
マジで?
It's going to come a lot.
めっちゃくるじゃん
Your friends will be very happy.
友達めっちゃ喜んでくるでしょ
I want a friend like that right now.
今そんな友達欲しいんだけど
I told her I would give her a massage, but she did.
マッサージしてあげるって言って してあげてるんですけど マッ
I was told to do a surge, but...
サ ージしてって言われて あーでも、
You might be asked to do it.
してって言われるかも
Now everyone knows that massage is good.
そしたらもう みんなマッサージが 上手いこと知ってるんだ
If you get a massage at a time like this, you'll instantly feel better.
こんな時期でマッサージされたら 一瞬に元気になっちゃう
Are you doing volunteer work?
ボランティアやってる?
volunteer?
ボランティア?
You can get money.
お金取れるじゃん
Well, certainly.
まあ確かに
I did it like a volunteer.
ボランティアみたいな 感じでやって
You're so kind.
優しいね
How do you massage your friends?
どんな感じでマッサージしてる 友達にするときは?
Well, I'm exhausted.
えーもうガッツリ
Thoroughly?
ガッツリ?
I'm rubbing it.
揉んでる
full.
いっぱい
Use oil?
オイル使って?
Do you use oil?
オイル使うんだ?
For massage.
マッサージ用の
Are your friends like this then?
その時は友達もこんな感じ?
Is this the situation?
こういう状況?
Isn't that naughty?
それはそれでエッチじゃない?
Your friend is not a man, right?
友達って男じゃないでしょ?
girl.
女の子
But when it comes to girls talking to each other, it's like this.
でも女の子同士で言ったら こんな感じでやってたらさ それは
That's naughty, isn't it?
それで エッチだよね
Don't you feel like we're friends?
友達感じちゃったりとかしないの?
Eh, what do you think?
えーどうなんだろう?
I won't make you look good.
エッコにしないよ
Because it's wet, it's not wet.
濡れてるから濡れてないから
do not.
しない
Does your voice sound suspicious?
声が怪しかったりとかしない?
Maybe not.
えーないかも
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
Well then, I want you to get rid of the bubbles.
じゃあ泡抜けになってほしい
I removed the bubbles.
泡抜かった
人生初解決
lol
笑
This is what he says at first.
最 初はこんなこと言ってくれるんだ
Oil?
オ イル?
That's right.
そうだよね
Tears wet.
涙ぬるする
ah
あー
Amazingly slimy.
すごい ぬるぬる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Is your hair okay?
髪の毛大丈夫?
stop?
止める?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
slimy.
ぬるぬる
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
I want it to be even more slippery, so apply it on my body, all over my body.
もっとぬるぬるしたいからさ 自分の体に塗って 全身で
Put your own drool on it with the oil and make it slippery.
オ イルと一緒にさ 自分のよだれを乗せてさ ぬるぬるさせて
It's so messed up with drool.
すごい よだれでくちゃくちゃ
Give me some in your mouth too.
口の中にもちょうだい
delicious.
おいしい
Yeah.
うん
I want you to put your feet on it.
足を置いてほしい
Hold it between your legs.
足 で挟んで
I want you to put your feet out.
足を出してほしいな
Yeah.
うん
I want you to slide your weight on my butt.
体重をさ、 お尻でさ滑ってほしいな
Turn your butt this way.
お尻こっち向けて
amazing.
すごい
My butt is bulging.
お尻がぽけしぽけ
Shake your butt.
お尻振って
My legs are terrible.
足やばい
Highest.
最高
Make your breasts feel nice and comfortable.
おっぱいでさ 心地よい気持ちよくして
It's so soft.
すごい柔らかい
My butt is bulging.
お尻がぽけしぽけ
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、 やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Awesome, let's go.
すごい、行く行く
I'm going
行ってる
Can you see where it's raised?
上げられたところ見える?
Can you see where you are?
自分が置かされてるところ見える?